You two seem to have a great relationship.
يبدو أن علاقتكما رائعة.
Should we put the photo up on the wall?
هل نضع الصورة على الحائط؟
No, I don't want to.
لا، لا أريد ذلك.
Why not?
ولم لا؟
Don't you want to make it public?
ألا تريد أن تجعل الأمر علنياً؟
Are you embarrassed to be with me?
هل تشعر بالحرج من التواجد معي؟
That's not it at all!
هذا ليس هو الأمر على الإطلاق!
Then why?
فلماذا؟
I just don't want to put it up.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أضعها.
So childish.
تصرف طفولي للغاية.
What's childish about it?
ما هو الشيء الطفولي في ذلك؟
Help us put it up.
ساعدنا في تركيبه.
Sure thing!
بالتأكيد!
President Qin.
الرئيس تشين
What is it?
ما هذا؟
This is what Secretary Lin sent me last night.
هذا ما أرسلته لي السكرتيرة لين الليلة الماضية.
What are you looking at?
ما الذي تنظر إليه؟
Go on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Where's Secretary Lin?
أين السكرتيرة لين؟
Seriously, Old Qin?
هل أنت جاد يا تشين العجوز؟
I'm your own daughter!
أنا ابنتك!
Why are you always thinking of others at a time like this?
لماذا تفكر دائماً في الآخرين في مثل هذا الوقت؟
You dislike me that much?
هل تكرهني لهذه الدرجة؟
Then I'm leaving.
ثم سأغادر.
What do you mean 'others'?
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "آخرين"؟
Isn't he your boyfriend?
أليس هو حبيبك؟
Him...
له...
We broke up.
انفصلنا.
Look at you.
انظر إليك.
I told you.
أخبرتك.
When you're in a relationship,
عندما تكون في علاقة عاطفية،
you have to be reasonable.
يجب أن تكون معقولاً.
Were you too willful again?
هل كنت عنيداً أكثر من اللازم مرة أخرى؟
Who can stand you being so self-centered?
من يستطيع تحمل أنانيتك هذه؟
Say something!
قل شيئا!
Exactly.
بالضبط.
It's all because you spoiled her.
كل ذلك بسبب تدليلك لها.
Look at this personality.
انظر إلى هذه الشخصية.
What do we do?
ماذا نفعل؟
She takes after you, I'm telling you.
إنها تشبهك، أقول لك ذلك.
I didn't tell you to criticize her.
لم أقل لك أن تنتقدها.
Why are you blaming me?
لماذا تلومني؟
Dad, Mom.
أبي، أمي.
I have work at the company, I'm leaving.
لدي عمل في الشركة، سأغادر.
Hurry up and arrange them for her.
أسرع ورتب لها الأمر.
Twenty meetings a day, you hear?
عشرون اجتماعاً في اليوم، هل تسمع؟
I refuse to believe not one will be suitable.
أرفض أن أصدق أنه لن يكون هناك أي شخص مناسب.
I can arrange thirty if I have to.
يمكنني تدبير ثلاثين شخصًا إذا لزم الأمر.
But Secretary Lin is a good person.
لكن الوزير لين شخص جيد.
He is a good person.
إنه شخص طيب.
But your daughter won't have it.
لكن ابنتك لن تقبل بذلك.
Why did she leave?
لماذا رحلت؟
Look what you did.
انظر ماذا فعلت.
So stubborn.
عنيد جداً.
Look at you.
انظر إليك.
I told you, when you're in a relationship, you have to be reasonable.
قلت لك، عندما تكون في علاقة، يجب أن تكون معقولاً.
Were you too willful?
هل كنتَ عنيداً أكثر من اللازم؟
You're so self-centered.
أنت أناني للغاية.
Who can stand you?
من يستطيع تحملك؟
I'm sorry, miss.
أنا آسف يا آنسة.
The park is closed for the day.
الحديقة مغلقة اليوم.
We're not admitting any more visitors.
لن نسمح بدخول المزيد من الزوار.
Sorry, sorry.
معذرة، معذرة.
She made a mistake.
لقد ارتكبت خطأً.
Please, go right in.
تفضل بالدخول مباشرة.
You stopped her?
هل أوقفتها؟
That's Young Master Lin's girlfriend.
هذه حبيبة السيد الشاب لين.
What?
ماذا؟
You didn't know?
ألم تكن تعلم؟
She was the one who came with him last time.
هي التي جاءت معه في المرة الماضية.
Then why did they come separately this time?
فلماذا جاؤوا منفصلين هذه المرة؟
Maybe...
ربما...
I hope Secretary Lin never leaves.
أتمنى ألا تغادر الوزيرة لين أبداً.
I love you.
أحبك.
Qin Meili.
تشين ميلي.
I can't hear you!
لا أستطيع أن أسمعك!
I love you!
أحبك!
Can't hear you!
لا أسمعك!
I love you, Qin Meili!
أحبك، تشين ميلي!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I don't want to go.
لا أريد الذهاب.
Don't pull me.
لا تسحبني.
Stop pulling me!
توقف عن سحبي!
I'm not going.
لن أذهب.
No way.
مستحيل.
I carefully picked out that bridesmaid dress.
لقد اخترت فستان وصيفة الشرف بعناية.
When did I agree
متى وافقت؟
to be your bridesmaid?
هل ترغبين في أن أكون وصيفة شرفك؟
I'm not going.
لن أذهب.
You're so heartless.
أنت عديم الرحمة للغاية.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'm not going.
لن أذهب.
To make up for last time's regret,
لتعويض ندم المرة الماضية،
and to prevent tragedy from happening again,
ولمنع تكرار المأساة،
we've decided to give you a big gift.
لقد قررنا أن نقدم لك هدية كبيرة.
Take this!
خذ هذا!
So incredibly childish.
تصرف طفولي للغاية.
Don't embarrass us.
لا تحرجنا.
We've already remarried.
لقد تزوجنا مرة أخرى بالفعل.
How can you talk
كيف يمكنك التحدث؟
so harshly still?
لا تزال قاسية إلى هذا الحد؟
I...
أنا...
That was just a reluctant compromise for the kids.
كان ذلك مجرد حل وسط متردد من جانب الأطفال.
Who isn't doing it for the kids?
من لا يفعل ذلك من أجل الأطفال؟
Hurry up and look.
أسرع وانظر.
Is this a bridesmaid dress?
هل هذا فستان وصيفة العروس؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I really didn't know
لم أكن أعرف حقاً
how to find you
كيف تجدني
without being rejected.
دون أن يتم رفضك.
Marry me.
تزوجيني.
Will you marry me?
هل ستتزوجني؟
Qin Meili.
تشين ميلي.
But I said...
لكنني قلت...
I...
أنا...
I accept.
أوافق.
I accept that I'm the one who was chosen.
أتقبل أنني أنا من تم اختياره.
Because you are Qin Meili.
لأنكِ تشين ميلي.
And I believe in Qin Meili.
وأنا أؤمن بـ تشين ميلي.
I do.
أفعل.
So sweet.
حلوة جدا.
That's...
هذا...
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
Nothing more?
لا شيء آخر؟
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
There has to be a wedding!
لا بد من إقامة حفل زفاف!
Right!
يمين!
Otherwise, all our
وإلا، فإن كل ما لدينا
hard work
العمل الجاد
was for nothing?
هل كان ذلك بلا جدوى؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Wrap it up, everyone.
انتهى الأمر يا جماعة.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Groom
زوج
Do you take this
هل تأخذ هذا؟
beautiful lady as your wife?
سيدة جميلة كزوجة لك؟
For better or for worse,
سواء كان ذلك للأفضل أو للأسوأ،
in sickness and in health,
في السراء والضراء،
to have and to hold,
أن يمتلك ويحتفظ به،
to love her,
أن أحبها،
to cherish her,
أن نعتز بها،
and to care for her,
وأن يعتني بها،
till death do you part?
حتى يفرقنا الموت؟
I do.
أفعل.
Bride
زوجة
Do you take
هل تتناول
Enough with the talk.
كفى كلاماً.
I do.
أفعل.
Then let's do it.
فلنفعل ذلك إذن.
We don't have the ring.
ليس لدينا الخاتم.
The ring.
الخاتم.
Okay.
تمام.
Grow old together.
نكبر معاً.
We're finally done, right?
انتهينا أخيراً، أليس كذلك؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
A new, beautiful chapter of life
فصل جديد وجميل من الحياة
is about to begin.
على وشك أن يبدأ.
Yes.
نعم.
My dear secretary.
سكرتيرتي العزيزة.